Profile

I am a skilled data analyst with a strong technical background in business intelligence and work history in data analysis. With around 2 years of experience in the field, I developed a solid grasp on business and strategy. Currently looking for a CDI (starting March '23).

Professional Experience

Data analyst, Naki Power

Jun 2022 - Dec 2022 | Paris, France

- Streamlined monitoring of KPIs for Operations/Marketing/Sales departments by designing and enhancing dashboards, resulting in significantly increased efficiency.
- Acted as primary point of contact for all data-related topics for 4 departments across 4 countries, including conducting in-depth analysis of business strategy.
- Advised and supported the Investor deck and data room design.
- Revitalized sales workflow by utilizing Google Places API data scraping to identify and prioritize potential leads (over 100,000) through classification and then feeding them through Pipedrive.
- Conducted A/B testing to optimize pricing strategy, leading to improved revenue per rental for services in Sweden by 50%.

Data Specialist, Amazon

Jul 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hyderabad, India

- · Conducted case-level analysis to identify predictors and root causes of business issues, leading to development of customer experience and delivery improvements.
- Generated data-driven reports and provided insights to stakeholders, facilitating informed decision-making and problem-solving.
- Analyzed metric issues related to customer delivery experience and identified root causes.
- Proposed viable solutions to improve performance based on analysis.
- Facilitated stakeholder understanding of complex data issues through clear communication and presentations.

Skills

Programming languages

Python, SQL, Javascript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Databases & Software

MySQL, Google BigQuery, Mongo DB, Snowflake, Google Cloud Platform, Microsoft SQL Server, Airflow, Hightouch, DBT, Asana, JIRA

Business Intelligence tools (BI Tools)

Power BI, Tableau, Looker Studio, Microstrategy, Stitch, SAP, Excel, VBA, Sheets.

CRM Tools

Salesforce, Pipedrive, Intercom, ClickUp

Projects

Instacart Customer Segmentation,

K-means clustering, machine learning, Python Created segments and calculated CLV and devised marketing strategies.

Chessmeta (Over 100,000 games +), Python, Pandas, Tableau EDA analyses of 100,000 games to understand the meta.

Sahit Sharma **BODDUPALLY**

Data analyst



sahitsharma.boddupally@ gmail.com

+33 7 69 05 84 78

Villejuif,France

Education

Masters in Business Intelligence & Analytics (Msc, BAC+5), ESC Clermont Business School Sep 2021 – Feb 2023 France

Bachelor of technology in Computer Science, **GITAM University** Jul 2014 – Jun 2018 | India

Languages

English

Hindi

French

Interests

- Chess
- Football
- Cosmology

Soft skills

Proactive

Autonomy

Organized

Teamwork